(Sheldon:)If I knew what that meant,
I might just do it.
(Howard:)I'm really glad
you're here.
(Howard:)Can we talk?
Sure.
(Penny:)So, you gonna get
up there later?
(Sheldon:)A microphone,
a room
(Sheldon:)full of inaccurate depictions
of Polynesian religion,
(Sheldon:)and a captive audience
to hear about it? You bet I am.
(Howard:)I'm sorry I freaked out
this morning.
(Howard:)I want you to know...
(Howard:)I'm done being scared.
(Bernadette:)It's okay to be nervous.
I am, too.
(Howard:)Thank God, 'cause I was lying...
you might not have to wait
(Howard:)nine months to see
someone soil their pants.
(Howard:)But I'm also
really excited.
(Howard:)I mean it.
(Amy:)Me, too.
(Howard:)I love you.
(Howard:)Mmm.
And I'm not just saying that
(Howard:)because your breasts
are gonna get bigger.
♪ Are we an item?
Girl, quit playin' ♪
♪ We're just friends ♪
♪ What are you sayin'? ♪